was just fine, slice my video.
Happy Friday.
So I'm still, my head is kind of spinning over what happened.
It was like, it just happened so fast.
Like I literally was, you know,
talking to Alex a couple of days ago on the show and,
you know, ever since we made up or whatever,
everything's been fine,
but I don't quite understand what happened.
You give you like a summary like what I'm still trying to figure it out. So, um
so we reconciled back in
in April
In early April soon after that, I guess
Brandon had started coming on the show and
Kind of like I guess she did a video. She's say oh what is psyche doing platforming predators blah blah
And then she came on my show. We had a good talk about it. She made like the
This video psyche's boys club. I wish I mean I now I can't play her stuff, you know, but
Unless she was to like tell me I could but I
Didn't like that boys club video and stuff and I love her stuff. I mean, it's like it. You know, I really
We it's like when it's good. It's good when it's bad. It's it's awful
But it's like when it's good. It's like we get along really really really well
And so that's why it's like I don't understand how it turned suddenly turned into like well what happened was
you know, she kind of, you know,
came forward and supported Brandon.
She has started a, started a, like a live one day.
I came on, I kind of got mixed more in the middle of it.
You know, Brandon and I had personal, like, you know,
just like, I like, I like him.
I mean, it's like, but we had some like personal
misunderstandings or, you know,
Whatever but I still don't hate him or anything and I had no problem with her
or anybody else becoming his friend or supporting or whatever but I just decided
to back off a little bit with the focus of the show so much on that stuff because
it was becoming a distraction I did see like signs that he could be the type to
to turn on people but
You can't say like that sometimes she's not like almost the same type a little bit sometimes. I don't know. I don't want to like
Exacerbate it make me her matter anything. I'd say I know I love her but it's like now to call me an extortionist to call me a
drug dealer
trafficker or whatever
It's just I mean it gets a little ridiculous. I don't know. I just hope I don't know what it is. I hope that
Everything's okay. I don't know. It's just confused. It just confuses me. I'm I backed off from her
I sent her a text message and I said, you know
She she got mad at me like what the first time because I didn't like, you know
Talked to her first or whatever, but she didn't come to me or say anything to me
I mean, she just didn't text message and say hey, you know, it's oh and then she just like she did everything
She's everything very publicly, you know, I mean, that's why I dox myself now. It's like she's doxing my name and stuff, you know
but
It wasn't anything, like I wouldn't have just disclosed or like been
I just I make an effort to like just step lightly and and let her
How she wanted to do I didn't I never asked her for anything or anything
Didn't tell anybody to ask her for I mean it's like so I don't understand this extortion part
I don't understand the drug the drug running thing. Maybe it's like cuz
Norcal is making a joke about oh, he wants me to send him a pound of meth and I was like, oh, sure, okay
Yeah, whatever, but I don't I don't not a drug dealer. I don't send drugs in the mail
FBI doesn't even need to bother if they do it's just wasting resources, but go ahead
You can check check my mail logs or whatever. I don't
Really, I'm like, I'm pretty boring in terms of other stuff. I just don't understand. Let me see what's going on in the chat
Yeah, so yeah, and I'm gonna watch you. Okay. Well, maybe I have an accent. I'm sorry. I next I'm sorry
I didn't see I was in the other screen. Hi. I'm sorry
Hey, I'm taking care of cat. I also had my youngest cat that got sick. I didn't say anything. I was concerned but
I have a neighbor that's a vet and she came over last night to help me with her because she's been sick the young one
I don't know what she ate, but she's fine now. So I'm happy
I was concerned because she was like in hiding and and and she told me she said well that that's you know
Let her you know, whatever
She give her some medicine and stuff and she said you know, she'll be like that, but she should be okay tomorrow
And guess what this morning? She's fine and she's with me right now
I was worried I was thinking you know cats usually hide when they say when they're about to die or something
Right, and she's too young, and I was thinking what's wrong with her, but no she's fine now
Yeah, sometimes they eat like
You know, there's a lot of flowers that are poisoned to get like lilies and stuff.
I don't have flowers in here, you know.
I gave her some treats, maybe it was that.
I don't know, because that's never happened before, but she's fine now.
She's crashed out, but she hid, you know, and it's like, yeah, I was worried.
But this morning, you know, I was, I thought, my God, I don't know.
I hope she's, she'll be okay now.
And then she came out and she's here and she's fine now.
Good, you know like normal, but before that she didn't even eat yesterday like she was sick. She just disappeared and you know
That's what they do. They get under they'll go into the bed. They'll go under like they go under
Yeah, stuff where it's dark, you know, so yeah, so then I let her be like that like my neighbor
vet said and I'm glad and she came over yesterday and
That can do that. I mean, that's awesome. That's what I like about that my neighbors
I got them involved with the rescue stuff and so they're all involved, especially
mostly the Spanish people
There's Lola. You know, so they help and we got rid of a lot of the feral cats by
rescuing them and
my friend who does a rescue, she came out before, this happened before,
she came out with all these
cages to take and loaded her
SUV with them.
So they were saved so yeah, I got there's good people around here
That's what I like about the people everybody goes out and feeds the we don't have that many feral's now
But they feed them and we take them to get fixed and stuff and most of us pay for it
I do most of the time
Well, I want to show you like that. Oh, so that you know, this person is obsessed with me
I like because you know, you know, I love my cats and my cats are yeah
Be well fed and stuff. I want to show you she made this like comic strip kind of thing with Lenore in it
I was like, oh, it looks like kind of like me and Lenore, but then I read it and it's like this is like the narrative
That is that they're trying desperately to push on me that I'm starving my cats. My cats are abused healthy
No, they're not that's what I hate about these trolls and stuff, you know, just don't show them on lives
Maybe yeah, I don't do that here
I share them in other like Facebook because I know those people and I have family there. We'll check this out
So the work hold on I've taken this burden
And let's try this. There we go. So you see there? Oh, that's so cute. Who did that? That's beautiful
Yeah, it's cute. Then it's but you read it and it's not so cute. It says it's from sweepy as she goes
Oh, no way. Are you serious?
It says hi there Lenore and then in ours she goes. Hello. Tell me human. Why have you not fed me yet?
Oh, no shit. I wish I could Lenore, but I'm too broke to buy you food and she goes hmm. I'm going
I'm leaving to go meet up with Trix,
to go meet up with Trix.
Okay.
Do I cat that round the way?
Oh no, wow.
You should just erase that there and then keep it.
That's a beautiful picture.
I can't believe they do that.
Yeah, because I had an older Pekingese.
He lived to 16 and a half years old.
And that's who the first cat I rescued.
It was because of him and the other peak that I had.
Um, you know that was years ago. Yeah, there's so uh, yeah, they love them
But y'all gosh and I miss him and I I posted to him on on youtube in the shorts and I got over 8,000 views on him
It was just a picture of him me leaving the vet the vets when he got his rabies shot
and
Oh, see that that's the one that looks like kitty and she she passed away. She was 20
Yeah, oh my god, I still miss her so much like he is like damn
It's just and I saw another young cat a feral cat and she looks he it's a he and he looks just like kitty
Oh, let's see if this is what she, yeah, this is my lap and she's great.
So, anyway, I had somebody make some fake profiles a couple years ago showing my dog
and saying, you know, my name and not Karen's dead dogs.
Oh, I am.
You know, that's fucked up.
It was Astrum on it, did that.
Oh, and I know you like, you know, helped her out a lot too.
I mean, it's like, whoa, that's what's-
Oh, yeah, that's my passion.
I love animals.
Yeah.
I mean it's like I can't I mean I just don't know like I've been like I've had so many broken
relationships on YouTube of people and it's like
the dates, sometimes they just go seem to go crazy on,
or they're not crazy.
They're trolls.
That's why everybody says be careful of them,
because my friend Nancy was ready to take a panel
with Alex, but she knew better,
because she warned me and she said,
you know, she flip flops a lot and also will turn on you.
But then she said, let me get a few days
and she's gonna watch her and look at what happened.
She just turns on everybody, lies and instigates and all.
You know and I and when she when she sent me the ad request
I only posted it to show that she sent that because she's talking shit about me when she went after we already argued
She still sent me a request a DM request for YouTube and but see before that
I already had two weird alts trying to send requests
Right, I didn't know how to block them then and that's the post I made about you know
That's what I said
I didn't say any names because it was to alt accounts before her
So I wasn't talking about her until I made the video
You know, I don't even know why she wanted to add me because she was already talking shit
And then she's talking to chicken cakes at Loser, who stalked, you know, Gia, who's
gone now.
And I don't like bringing her up because she passed away.
But the truth was that Gia got back with an ex who was still married.
And you know, they they did coke and and you know, I guess fentanyl and
Passed away and scaly talked about it because he talked to her before it happened and he was worried about her and they said she never woke up
Yeah, and I say I don't think I mean it's like and then they keep trying to bring your name into that like it's like
Yeah, it's like you had nothing to do with any of any of the reason that
I mean, it's like, you know, I mean, it's all the recordings because I haven't let I did leave her message yesterday
I guess she posted that too just but I didn't threaten her or anything
So I don't know because I have recordings of her that's going in discord
So she needs to shut up especially that call that sounded whacked out
And and it's already being posted on one of the discord. So it's being passed around
Fubar.com. There's you know, like I said celebrities are there
And that guy that she owes money to a baseball pro expo. He's even there
But and he's gonna send me stuff because he sued her and
Trisha posted that he sued her a lot of money
thousands and thousands of dollars
For her services that he could get the certain that she ripped him off
And Trisha had posted that
I mean, there was no I mean it's like because I that day I had talked to her, you know
And then the morning is on the show and stuff and then she did the show about I guess it was about
Mimi and Carl and stuff and then then I had the bread incident and I just just kind of silent during it
I was just like and but I was like, you know gonna just privately or you know quietly have a talk
But then it's like all of a sudden
doing it live now i'm an extortionist yeah she's saying about brandon and he just texted that she
needs to give him a thousand dollars donation he's not her intern he's he he took offense to that
he does his own streams he's doing good on his own yeah gamer and a streamer
And I guess she reached out to him or, I mean, I don't know how they reached out, I guess because he was in the chat and you know, it's just crazy that she does this and acts like she's cool with you and then just turns on everybody because everybody warned me.
Even that friend that was going to join and she's going to give it a few days because she sees how she is in her reputation.
And look at what happened. And I thanked her today because she messaged me. She said I told you be careful of her and
I said, you know what? I'm proud of you for stating on your word that you don't want to be be involved with any of these nuts
Right. I mean, I just I mean, it's just kind of like out of
It's just shocking. It's hurting because it's like I did like, you know, I did humble myself last time and to an apologize and
Even if I don't feel like it was entirely like my fault for the fault, but it's like and then it's like like clockwork. It has to like
It's like musical chairs or something like that.
The music's good.
Provide her.
She's the worst one out of everybody.
You wouldn't believe the messages
and you know that I'm getting everywhere,
including IG about her.
And you know, you should have been careful.
You should have been, and I was thinking,
you know what I should have, but I trusted her.
And I remember she turned on you for being friendly
with Bita and there she is jumping on panels.
I've never known somebody so two-faced.
Yeah, and she does is all the time and they call her a flip flopper and all and
You know, it's just ridiculous and I went ahead and joined
Crystal's live she had a good live last night and Gamble was there
So yeah, we made peace and I appreciated him for you know, I reminded him. Hey, you defended me a while back and
Yes, you remember that
Launch crystals last night and then she like brought me up and she's like what makes me think that I would let you
On my show ever and I said well you let me up right now, and then she's like kick me off and
I don't know. She's like she just hates me. She says I'm an animal abuser
You know going with the narrative that you know that people are saying it, you know
And it's like, you know, even I like you know kind of like trying to go easy on her for the decline stuff because
you know, that's kind of
more of a nuanced topic but it's kind of like you know I don't know they're just getting into like
They just think they just know that like you know, my cats are like my kids
But then it's like they won't even give them and they think they didn't like they care so much
But they don't and they're like, oh those are just animals. They're not your kids. They're not they're not there
They're like kids to me. I love animals
You know, and she's great with her cat. I mean that cat's so happy and spoiled that cat doesn't care if it was declawed
I think he's having more fun now
And he was a baby, I think, when he had it done.
So I saw her when she bought him home after that was done.
The cat was fine.
Yeah, like indoor cats, they're completely indoor.
It's not maybe the biggest.
I mean, I'd say, like, you know,
if they ever worked to be outdoor cats,
I know it's like a kind of-
Yeah, and that's not an outdoor cat.
Yeah, but there's people that do it and let their cats out
and that's horrible.
Let them run out all over the place or-
themselves and things like that that's kind of like taking away their like yeah and that's why
that cat is so happy and and safe and she spoils him and you know and and he's got toys a cat tree
you know she has a she even has a thing that where he can sit up by the window to look out
and lay down yeah you know i was surprised because she's she's doing great with him has toys and
things for him for that cat she adores that cat that's the happiest cat i've ever seen
You know spoiled baby and if I've ever called someone like you know, I did mine. It's a crystals. Like I said
Oh because she likes Q
Hey, I asked Rose's sacred. Yeah, cuz she likes Q. I was like why I was like, well, I
Oh, it's it's a Eliza. Hi Eliza. Yeah
Yeah, I did say like, oh, you know, I've said beat is a PDF
I've said she's a but it just like in joking because they all say they keep saying I'm PDF protector and stuff like that
Which is yeah, that's it. Yeah, some people got angry. Yeah
I was like cuz they go you're a PDF and then they say like a second later. They go protect her
And so it's kind of like trying to like put the association, right? It's like they're trying they're trying I mean desperately
It's like it's just so slander so and it's like so I wish I could
You know on it's hard to deal with things online said because it's like, you know
I guess we were watching you saw that that last night when I posted it with the blackout Andy, right?
Where he was like you got arrested twice and then you thought I saw that you didn't show the whole thing
Is it still up? I wanted to see what happened rumble. It's on rumble. Yeah, he ends up like getting arrested again
He gets arrested twice in that video
Like he uh, what because well the first time he kept going up to the police and like, you know
videotaping them when they were arresting someone and then he was trying to go away
And then he kept walking back and like talking and he said he said that one of the guys looked like trident IRL
They got arrested real quick
And then he decides to go the same day he goes back to the exact same place
And he starts drinking in the park in the middle of the night or so. Oh my god
Yeah, the middle of the night, um, he's like drinking and then the guy, then he gets arrested again because the cop comes up and he's like, drop, don't, don't, don't drop it. Don't pour it out now.
And he's like, I'm not getting arrested again. Am I? And he's got arrested again because he's the same place antagonizing the police.
So it's crazy.
He always gets arrested.
Yeah, he's a little bit nuts. That guy killed somebody when he was drunk, I think, and it was a car accident, not on purpose.
But the person passed away and, you know, he was arrested for that, but he was drunk.
He was drunk.
But somebody ended up dying in that car wreck.
It was a car wreck.
I wonder if he feels remorse or anything for that.
I mean, you would think that...
Oh, my God.
And go back to drinking?
I would never drink again.
I wouldn't be able to forget that.
Yeah, I mean that's intense. I mean that's really intense to have a family. Lucky is not, you know, for a particular manslaughter, you know.
I mean I'm sure there's a lot of people in these communities that have done terrible things and it's like most of them are, that's why they're completely anonymous.
We don't know who a lot of these people are. They could be the same people, some of them, because I know people have alts and stuff and they go around.
Doing sock puppet accounts and stuff. It gets so complicated here, but they can feel I think you know anything like oh
Yeah, cuz he was saying oh well
He's like what would well I know that of course Victoria J didn't call the police on him, but he was like
Trying to report her and he's like he's like well, they won't do anything cuz she's in Canada. I mean, yeah
She's in a different country. I mean, so it does make it more difficult to prosecute for like standard when someone's in a different country
I mean, it's impossible pretty much and so
I mean, that's why the internet is just perfect for these trolls.
It's like, it's like, it's just like, it's so...
Yeah, it's all it is, it's trolls, you know, it's it's, and YouTube, was it like that before?
They didn't, that's why they need to stop with a lot of this or be stricter, you know,
because YouTube was only like for just music or videos, like shows and things like that,
not live streaming. They had some different type of live streaming and these were like professional.
Live streamers, you know, not anybody can get on and it's mostly weirdos and
You know crazy people
Go ahead. No, but you know because um, you know
Basically anybody with a camera now can can you know develop an audience and
And so and a lot of but a lot of the people that are like these these like really slick popular
Streamers that are more popular and stuff. A lot of them got get co-opted by like the Chinese government or other
Yeah, and they basically I mean or other government organizations and become they basically become become shills for the government
They basically just trade over their popularity their clout to start promoting the messages of these other countries and stuff like that
So you have to worry about some of these really popular streamers. I think we have anybody can
Kind of make a name for themselves. I mean like most people like Howard Stern had to go to broadcasting school for years and then work
Yeah, and then he was mad because all of a sudden there are people being able to work from home doing all the exact
Maybe a bigger audience sometimes, you know than him
Like basically that didn't do any of the work, but I mean
or it's about, you know, it's about public, the public opinion, I guess, of it and which is also
difficult to deal with, you know, because of the public. Yeah, crazy. I remember a couple years ago,
I shared this video about this Chinese girl and she had a bunch of followers and she was pretty
much famous and she was in China and then she started getting trolled so bad and she met up with
two different guys that used her, one of them I think practically assaulted her and then they were
harassing her on YouTube when she'd go live and calling her a ho and all this stuff and
She took her life right there on lives
Oh, she was a young girl and then the story came out about what happened to her. It was sad
It's awful. Like I actually watched this documentary on YouTube and it's it's called like the the darkest YouTube rabbit hole
And it's called the capper you heard of this. No the capper. Yeah
And she never looked up with those two guys. She just met them on a live
And they went back and made rumors and they were just starting to bully her very bad just bad and that's what the cappers did the cappers were these people and they're like a lot of them are in Europe or they're all over but they're these and they're this kind of like a they were a YouTube group at one point or whatever and they would do they go to these the teenager.
chat rooms and then they would coerce like the some teenage girls or whatever to
Flash the camera and they would take that and then they would start to blackmail them and they would send it to their schools
Oh, I heard that they that yeah, that was um, and yeah, I heard about the
Boy that just took his life because of that they took his picture and it was actually a man pretending to be a girl
And then his parents found that he took his life.
Yeah, I mean, that's what they, I mean, it's like, it's so sad because it's like,
even the people like around them, they'll, they'll like, you know,
they'll sort of take the, these, these blackmailers side, and this is like,
because these are underage people that they're sending, and then,
but the thing with the cappers is that they had this award show and they would sell it.
who who unalive themselves and things like that. I mean, it's like that's how it was like a cartoon award show that they would do with a real weird voice
I can show you
It's called the capper that's on YouTube or it's it's another it's it was on YouTube
I mean that now they still have all the videos up around Vimeo, but I can show you like a little bit about God how weird
Yeah, it's like because it was like there's this cartoon on HBO that they stole and then they would start using this lady's voice
Oh, do you want to watch a little bit about it? I'll show you a little yeah. That's mine. Yeah. Yeah
It's really here with my cat. I'm she's healing. It's really terrible. I gotta leave in a couple hours. Oh, yeah
Worst stories you might see good day brave little toaster. So everybody this is about the camper
This is like a really be like very just be aware of like where people, you know, like and it's like, you know
Don't get mad at people if they
you know they they get like you know they're picture taken and stuff like that online
it's like they get bullies in despair they can't move they can't do anything
this is a sad story here you go i'll bring it right up there you go okay this is the cappers
A 15-year-old girl uploads a video to YouTube documenting her ongoing struggle with cyberharassment and blackmail, being done at the hands of an unnamed individual.
Throughout the video, not a single word is spoken. Instead, the teen tells her story through dialogue written on paper cards, flipping through them one by one, painting a picture of the traumatic abuse she was living through.
Just over one month later, she would be dead as a direct result of that very harassment.
The story of Amanda Todd is one of the most heartbreaking across all of YouTube, with
the case sending ripples not only across the site, but across the world as well, with the
fallout still being felt to this very day.
And from this case, a light was briefly cast on one of the darker corners the internet
has ever seen, momentarily illuminating a community that was never meant to be seen
by the public eye, with the rabbit hole even more bizarre than anything we've covered
on this channel before.
We're diving down to its very depths.
Before we dive into this incredibly dark topic, I chose not to do a sponsor on this one as it just
didn't really feel right. But if you want to support the channel, I do have a Patreon page
that offers some exclusive benefits. For example, less censored versions of videos like
Moderation was at its most primitive, and nefarious activity ran rampant,
with many of the worst examples coming from the dawn of live streaming.
Back then, streams in their associated chats were almost entirely unregulated, leading
to them becoming a cesspool of all sorts of degeneracy, and it's within one of these
very sites where Amanda's torment would begin.
It happened on a website called BlogTV, where Amanda had logged in one evening at the age
of 13 to the tune of 200 viewers, and it was here that she would be pressured to eventually
f**k the camera with a whole chat cheering her on, a decision that she would regret not
only in the moment, but for the remainder of her life.
Lurking in the chatroom was a man under the alias of Tyler Boo, who had been waiting
for that very opportunity to grab a screenshot and recording of this young girl in her most
vulnerable moment before immediately turning around and using that image as blackmail in
an attempt to leverage it for more private performances.
It was a demand that Amanda refused, though truthfully it wouldn't have mattered anyway.
as Tyler would turn her world into a living hell of online harassment, with a photo and video being
sent to all of her friends, acquaintances, and family members. It got so bad that on multiple
occasions her entire family would be forced to move, though this was of no use. As Tyler's
evil crusade persisted, every new school, every person she interacted with would eventually be
And with nowhere left to turn, she would take up drinking and drug use just to cope,
until eventually, on October 10th, 2012, she just couldn't take it anymore.
The story of Amanda Todd is a complex, tragic tale, with many factors ultimately playing
a role in her untimely passing, with none being more prominent than her harasser.
And with her video gaining immense virality following her passing, all eyes were on Amanda's
case, with a big question being, who is Tyler Boo, a question that leads us to a particularly
disturbing discovery, and today's main topic.
As to unmask this abuser, we have to first recognize that he wasn't alone, but rather
was part of one of the most bizarre and deranged communities ever uncovered on the internet.
Yeah, that's interesting.
With these headlines, Canadian authorities quickly began work on their investigation,
dedicating a team of detectives to unmask the man behind the Tyler Boo alias.
And there, it's likely that they discovered that the crimes Tyler had committed were far
more common than you would imagine.
Back then, Tyler was what is known as a capper, someone who prowls livestreams of young women
and men across the internet, egging them on into performing some type of lewd act.
and upon convincing them to perform said act, these cappers would then take screenshots
or recordings, also known as caps, immortalizing the moment in an image or short video.
For some cappers, this is where their involvement ends, but for many others, it goes much deeper.
Once in possession of the caps, they will then use this as blackmail against the victim,
And she wasn't alone.
Back then, this kind of stuff happened on a freakishly regular basis, with hundreds
even thousands of cappers operating on a given night, with their list of victims being essentially
immeasurable, victims who had their lives completely and utterly destroyed by these
malevolent outside forces that forbade them from ever speaking out, and these forces rarely
In reality, many of these cappers were closely intertwined within a community of individuals
sharing this common practice, many of whom shared techniques, caps, and genuine online
connections with each other. And as dark as this all may seem, their actual doings are somehow even
worse than you could fathom, a fact that would only be fully understood and laid out on a silver
Sorry to interrupt this is important. I was a little bit shooter. Yeah, yeah, that's interesting
That's I don't understand why the parents don't keep their kids off. You know off the site
Block it out or something and camera close welcome to the week in review of the daily cap her
The short-form program began its run here on YouTube back on June 20th, 2010,
and continued airing weekly for over a year, with each episode having a runtime of roughly 5 minutes,
primarily featuring this uncanny host in her robotic voice.
And if she looks vaguely familiar, you might recognize her, or even the layout in general,
as having come from the old HBO series Crashbox, an educational program made for children,
which features an eerily similar segment called Distraction News.
But the Daily Capper was a much different show, as its creators stole the imagery from Crashbox
and dubbed over it with this off-putting text-to-speech in order to tell the top weekly stories from
The capping world is a world that is unknown and mysterious to some, but really there's
nothing mysterious about it.
The Daily Capper is here to report, week by week, what goes on in the capping world.
The page is almost like a time capsule, preserving the wrong-doings of this otherwise obscure community and putting it all out in the open.
And because of this, investigators were understandably immediately drawn to the program as it quite literally documented all of the highlights in the capping community,
even discussing some of the group's major players and victims at the time that Tyler Boo had been harassing Amanda.
And thus began their deep dive, and ours as well, into the daily capper, in what better place to start than at the very beginning.
We are halfway through the year and what better way to spend 365 days then done your computer screen looking for camera ports?
Despite what others think, summer is not the time to go outdoors swimming being with friends.
Rather it is a time for girls and boys to turn their computers on and get dirty.
The show opens on a jarring note, with its creator being so crass that some might mistake
this as a work of satire, though sadly this is far from the case, which becomes evident
after only a few minutes when the tone is set for just how disturbing the Daily Capper
was going to be.
These are some highlights from this past week.
Nicole 34 went to Tiny Chat and exposed her 15 year old daughter.
Throughout the episode, multiple stories are told about what the capping community had
been up to, with the host referring to the acquisition of these caps as
Epic wins, a common phrase throughout the capping community, a true indicator of the
time period in which the show had aired.
But what makes this all the more chilling was that each of the girls that have been featured
on the show were minors, with the creator making sure to mention their ages, like a
Epic Wind was delivered in the form of four 13-year-old girls from Blanc TV Jr. and all
for a room of 300.
A hero went on cam and streamed their video for them.
These girls remain the most talked about girls in the capping world.
With these children bearing the brunt of the community's blackmail that week.
It was all laid out in black and white, not only did this one episode alone prove the
existence of the capping community, but it also showed us a glimpse into how they operate,
who they truly are, and just how remorseless they can be.
It's truly unlike anything I've ever seen on the internet, a group so clearly committing
wrongdoings yet so shamelessly airing it out, and I truly believe that whoever was behind
the Daily Capper never meant for this show to leave their little bubble.
with the very first episode alone including callbacks and past references to the capping
community with no added context being given.
Showing us that, A, the community had been around long before the Daily Capper, and B,
that the viewers were expected to have prior knowledge of events from within the community,
making it apparent that the program was made solely for involved cappers, which is likely
why it comes off as so unapologetic, especially as the episodes go on, as things only devolve
further from here.
Well, yeah, but it's like, it's still up on Vimeo.
I guess they put the things on Vimeo and so.
Wow.
Oh, look it, there's that stupid sweet peas in the room.
I'm just gonna bet ban her real quick.
She calls me a predator protector.
And then someone says, weird choice in content.
Okay, well.
No, no, don't put them up.
I don't wanna.
uh argue with anybody. I'm not putting them, I'm just banning them from the chat. I'm just banning
them from the chat. Yeah, that's crazy. Yeah, the protector. Yeah, that's what they were calling
me too. And then Alex, they said she posted that he's not, he's not a pedo. Yeah. You know, and
I don't know what Gamble would say to that because he's saying something different. Well, Gamble says
is like, um, Gamble says anybody like under the age of 18 is considered pedophilia. And like,
point it's called a fibophilia when it has to do with teenagers it's like a kind of because it's
like you know every but they're trying to make it so I mean the thing is it's like they can say
they'll say like oh a 40 year old man marrying a 20 year old woman is now pedophilia or something
yeah because there's no proof of him actually getting uh I'm talking about uh right
you know brandon there's no proof of him getting with any kid you know exactly and it's like you
know so they're trying to say oh well he's he talked to them on the internet and blah blah blah
i mean it's like you know because he was on this monkey app where this and then there was this drunk
Yeah, a schoolgirl or whatever and then he said like you know, they make you talk to them for 30 seconds
No, one of my channels dying Melissa. Well, Melissa if you want to say something you can actually like you know
Send a TTS or donation if you want your comments, right? Okay, so what the fuck happened with us are followed with Alex
Okay, what the fuck happened with that Melissa? Is that the one that goes by that Melissa? Yeah, this Melissa. Yeah
Yeah, I remember her turning on her so quick and doxing her and everything's did she didn't need to go there
She, you know, Melissa didn't do anything. It's just she just went nuts. And it's the same time turned on me when she was telling people she wanted to take me out to
Olive Garden
Or a red lobster and let me know because we had already had a falling out when I barely knew her and I was surprised
And and she did that and she was acting like she's cool. But this is what she does
I've never seen anybody flip-flop in the way she turns on people
I'm never gonna do this again with her. That's there's something wrong, you know
Yeah, and someone's asking like what happens like I still don't really understand
It just happened that that
She was lying about Brandon was we were trying to extort money from her
He was upset because she makes him look like a punk saying he's her intern. He's no intern. She does she think she is
She's just a streamer
Right, I think she was being a little bit tongue-in-cheek and like kind of trying to be cute about you know
She was trying he took offense to that and he said
Yeah, I mean yeah, and he is like a little bit of a hothead a little bit. Yeah, he is I told him about that
Yeah, he does you know, but I mean that's him and and he's a hothead because he's he's being sincere
He's defending himself against that right I know and it's like I think that the thing is it's like you know
Alex and I didn't get really kind of go out on a limb for him and you too
I mean it's like I mean because it's like there was like, you know, not not even a lot of people that were
we're having him on their shows and now it seems like he's gotten a little bit, at least got his
story out, at least got more people listening and stuff, but just for him to kind of like,
you know, it's like kind of like biting the hand that feeds you a little bit. It's like I was trying
to be kind, kind of gentle and he gets any, I think because of trauma, you know, he kind of like
Exactly. That's what we all do, though. I know I do.
Yeah, it's part of it. Yeah, I do it. I mean, we all do it.
And so that's why it's kind of like, yeah, go ahead.
Yeah. And a good friend of mine was actually finally going to maybe join her panel about
something else, but she didn't trust her because she warned me. She said, and I said, no, we're
cool. We're cool. She's cool.
And she said, give me a few days.
And then she saw her nice post about me.
She goes, oh, OK, well, she seems cool.
I'll give her a chance.
And then she saw her blasting me and Brandon out, you know?
And I mean, and she's playing old recordings because I
didn't leave recent recordings.
I did leave one a few nights ago, the last one.
But I have a lot of shit on her and also the recording
about her sister.
I didn't share that.
Yeah, you know, it was bad because she was going at her sister
She plays a victim and her she doesn't get along with her sister or with her mom and blames it on her dad
You know, I don't want to go into that but it just she she doesn't have friends in real life
It seems to be hiding just like Tommy said and I defended her for Tommy
I went out and reached out to him while he was live on that phone number
And she appreciated it and made a post about it. And then she's gonna go nuts on me. We could have talked it out
But I had trolls trying to send me a message or whatever and I was I didn't know how to block it till
And then I got hers, but that message wasn't to her. I just and then I thought
Maybe that's not even her because one of them, you know kept on
And uh, so I I blocked her and then all of a sudden she went nuts because I wasn't sure and that's why when she was attacking me
That's why I said look at this you try to add me but you know I would have accepted it if I knew it was really her but before that it was to them and one of them made an alt I think it was a Skelly alt or something and now we have NorCal in the room NorCal.
Okay, you know what I don't want him up with me that old man I'm not 70 years old you saw my real picture NorCal Matt.
You're just shady as fuck and everybody clips you and you got a kid and you need to be careful because you're drunk all the time again.
And they're showing your picture you're probably seventy i'm nowhere near seventy asshole you saw my picture.
Yeah, he was the one that said oh send me some method in the mail or something. And so I think
You up I clipped that yeah, he was telling Kate bragging, you know that he was fucking with you
And said that I clipped it. Yeah, I clipped cake you everybody sees him and they clip him nobody can stand them including Alex
But yeah, his information has been out. He's got a kid and and here he's causing shit
He's drunk out of his mind and talking shit. I blocked him a couple years ago and he went nuts on Rick's
Oh, he's getting me blocked and he's just nothing but a piece of shit. He's a drunk
He was drunk and so I have that clip where he's talking shit about me and remember I called him out a year ago
I embarrassed him and I'll do it again
Well, he's mad. I posted a picture of him when he accidentally showed himself on camera, but he's been on my show
Oh, I have it I'll post it so fuck him because he's talking shit about me when he has my recent pic
Right and they're using a picture from 2016. I was always thin before that
You know, I'd lost my mom. I had a hard time with it
And and then I blew up and I lost all that by 2018 because when when I got big like that
Psyche they were saying I was getting diabetes to high blood pressure
So I pulled myself together and lost that weight and I did by 2018 even now when I show pictures like when I was at the doctors
Everybody's they're like wow you're too thin and when I was went to ICU a year ago, and then I had they transferred me to the
physical rehab facility for two months
Um, and because I almost died and so I had to learn to walk again
It's like and and it was two months and and Sherry beat his friend
She was on the phone with me when I was saying goodbye to the patients
And she heard that one that was across from my room in a wheelchair and she was like
Oh, I'm sorry to see you go and stuff and I showed her that picture from 2016 and she's like
Who is that and I said that was me in
2016 and she looked me up and down she goes wow you look great
I said, yeah, I lost all that a long time ago and she says, but now you're a little too thin
And my doctor said I need to gain 10 pounds. It's like shit. I get sometimes I gotta smoke weed to eat
You know, and I'm trying but I'm very active now and I feel great
It's a thing
My nails like if my nails were dirty one day like they're dirty forever, but it's like, you know, my nails clean like, you know
It's like so it's like
You know nails can be clean like people can take a shower, but it's like they constantly try to like, you know dehumanize or
Or to put a negative association with people. What does she do with all this all the skin?
Well, I don't know. I mean, it's like she wants to go into that she can
What skin like, you know, sometimes there's excess skin when you know, you know what I don't that's why that lady was shocked
And that's why they get shocked when I see that old picture even my my
brother but
When I went to the ICU and I went to the physical rehab, he was mad at me when I called him and he
goes, is that how you lost all that weight? And now, and then when I got sick, I lost more.
I said, what are you talking about? He goes, are you doing meth with Larry the meth head,
And he was like, you know, you're doing meth.
That's why you lost it.
And you know, and I blocked him, but when I was discharged,
I went straight to their place the next day to confront him.
And he opened the door, kind of like, you blocked me.
And then he looked at me and he goes, well, you look great.
And I said, look at my face.
Do I look like a meth head?
I said, I've never seen or touched meth or anything.
And then he was happy to see me and he come down and smile and he goes I was kidding. No, he wasn't he wasn't kidding
So yeah, we're good now and now he apologizes and stuff. So
You know, and I don't have that skin
I can show you the picture of my legs and arm because they saw that and they're like wow you look great. Yeah, it's me
Athletic I was athletic. I wasn't big like that for long. I was athletic on my life
I'll show you pictures of me in college and it's like, you know, usually cuz you were maybe over 200 pounds
That's not going to give you a lot of excess skin if you lose it.
I mean, they're talking about like 600 pounds.
They like lose 400 pounds that they might have like this. Oh, no, and you know what?
You know what pissed me off? There's this guy and I use young a little too young and
He lived on the other side of the complex that I was at and I never met him before and and it was weird because
Before I moved he came over with the bowl of
He made Cuban food or something rice. He goes. Yeah, you need to eat and all this stuff
And I took it in and then we smoked some weed he had weed and you know then then he start coming over and
And he goes, uh, yeah, you're you're looking good and stuff. You don't look your age and he's only 28
And you know, we wanted to hang out a lot and I was telling him about the hospital because I still had the walker that I
That he took for his mom because he said his mom is on the walker
He took it and he goes and I said man, I used to be big a few years ago and you know 2016 2015 and 2016
And he goes, yeah, I know I remember and I said what and I said
I've never noticed it's seen you and he says no
I remember I've been living here for a while
I just moved closer to where you're at and I just took offense
It's like so why are you coming to talk to me when I hang out and stuff and you ignored me then?
You know, it was like them well, he was down now. He's interested. Yeah now. He's interested and comes over
You know, and it's like man, what would a jerk because he saw me then and never said hi
I don't that's weird and all of a sudden he was bringing Cuban food coming over to smoke weed and let's hang out
You know, he goes are you going somewhere? I
Want to take you a new car?
And, you know, I got vapes from him. He gave me vapes, you know, and then after that, I thought, I don't trust him.
He knows like why are you so interested now and then you know it's like shit
It's like and you were here all this time. I mean hell
Well, I have a friend that like she I guess she got a delivery from a from a streamer friend on her birthday and stuff
And then she got real excited and she gave like the grub hub delivery guy
I guess she got flowers or something and he had the delivery a hug and and brought him in and say look
Here's my friend and he joined I guess the discord
But then, a few weeks later, he sent her a dick pic.
Like and she is a little bit of older lady and stuff like that and like a single lady and she was just like kind of freaked out by
I mean, it was kind of a crazy story. I mean some good guys guys are pigs
You know like a lot of her and this is another thing that happened
I'd like to smoke weed and I was on my
Balcony with my pets and I saw this young guy and he was smoking weed and I said well, that's that's not
Smells like good weed and he goes you want to smoke and I said sure
So he jumped off the balcony and came over to my place and so we smoked and you know that was all i wanted to do and then he started getting up and then he went to close my curtains on the balcony window so nobody can see in.
And he started taking his clothes off, Psyche.
They were taking his clothes off, and it was like,
what the hell are you doing?
And he said, you're not interested.
I'm a dancer and all this stuff.
I kicked him out of there.
And then he started blowing me up.
He tried to come over and I wouldn't answer the door
and he blew me up.
So I called the number and his mom answered.
I guess it was her phone.
I said, look, I'm calling for, his name was Ricky.
I said, he's coming over too much and calling.
And I mean, I didn't know what to say
because it was her that answered the phone
and it was just getting too much.
So he's been pissed at me since then, but he still tries to talk, you know, and he'll
just, you know, just, yeah, it was just weird.
I don't know, he sounds like a guy that lives with his mom nearby you.
No, he visits his mom a lot.
He has to go someplace, he's 28, you know, and then now he hangs, he was hanging out
right outside in the balcony because my window.
My bedroom window was out there. I'm glad I moved though, you know, he's just yeah, I think he took a fence
You know and he's been pissed off at me
Well, do you have like delivery service? I mean, that's what I use delivery service
I don't know if you have like weed delivery services
No, because it's not legal here. So you can't but I do get it from my brother. He gets it
Yeah, and then that guy the the cuban guy. He brought me some vapes. He buys him someplace
But he said no, you don't need to pay for it here. It's it for you
It's not yeah, but I'm moved from there especially that young guy. He was like not the other one. I was trying to strip
I guess he thinks he's so hot, you know, it's like, man, that was just rude though, you know
I don't even know you your little kid when I need these guys like where are these guys jumping off their balconies
You know coming smoking me with me. I don't understand like I mean gosh
Yeah, he jumped off the balcony because they're on the second floor and then he ran out to my door and
Stuff and I'm thinking cool. We're gonna smoke weed and then he did that. It's like the fuck, you know, I mean
Yeah, weird. So yeah, I called his mom. I didn't know was her that was gonna answer it, you know
Yeah, to make him stop because he kept coming trying to come over
But until NorCal to add me on IG he'll see now
Don't have any hanging skin and my legs are back to great
I mean especially my legs because I've always been a cyclist and I was a racquetball
Say my pro player in my 20s
Uh-huh. Oh, wow. And I did the micathons and all all that stuff and then after my mom died
I just gave up on everything psyche. I didn't care anymore. I was drinking like a
24 cases soda every day
I think and my dad used to get pissed and when he'd come over he said oh you just have all this sugar all this coke in your fridge
You know, you're gonna die. You're getting diabetes and you know now. Yeah, so
That's what happens. I'm happy. I have a lot of energy when I was so big like that psyche when my car broke down.
And, uh, you know, I walked home.
I couldn't even make it a block. I had to sit down. That's how bad it was.
Wow. Now I have all this energy. I walk fast. I'm even jogging now two miles at the high school track.
So yeah, my legs are firm, but I was lucky with my legs because my dad had great legs.
And now my sister, who is the model, she's gaining the weight.
You know and it's sad because she tells me oh you look great Karen
I'm like you've lost a lot and you know I took I went over there by bike and she said what you rode your bike
Cuz it's we're an hour away, and I said yeah
I said I feel good and she was telling me I look great and she said I think I want to do that too Karen
I you know one day I think I want to get a bike
That was like two years ago, and she's still you know
I don't know. Maybe she's depressed or something, but she's still beautiful.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was just looking at that picture of my arm because I have a bruise when they take blood from me
and they said because I need to drink more water. I'll show it to you because everybody's more worried about,
wow, I'm skinny. It's like, well, I'm showing you what happened to my arm.
I was concerned because I you know, I was getting barousis from them taking blood
They hardly couldn't get any blood from me because they said I was too dehydrated too, and I have to keep up on water
Yeah, Apollo if you want to come up. I don't know if you know Apollo Apollo's real nice. He's like a Greek guy
Yeah, Paula can go and then Norkel add me on on IG that way you'll see and you did get my recent picture
That was a FaceTime picture. I have hair. I'm not bald
She's putting bald a eyes of me. It's like, you know, it's like I don't I have wavy hair all the way down to my shoulders
I've always had it like that. Yeah
Yeah, oh, and some of the people are there's trolls in the chat, but of course that's nothing losers. Yeah trolling or whatever
Like I know I mean well me too. It's like I've been told like you know my my hair like I've like my hairline's been the same since forever
I know it's like yeah, I have a little bit it goes back a little bit. Oh, we have baby. Oh, we have Brandon and Q coming up
Hold on a second. Okay
Yeah, you got hair Brandon has hair and a lot of people a lot of guys. I guess they're going bald
Like my I'm like, you know, Cyrax levels now
Cyrax actually has like cross-eyed his teeth are all fucked up his like, you know
He's retarded and he has like scabs on it. I thought you ran
Yeah, Karen, you know, they only did that to piss me off, right?
That's the only reason why they talk to you. That's the only reason
Yeah, I mean, I'm sorry, but it's when I saw the dog, you know, I'm passionate about animals though
You know cuz it really happened to the dog
They're full of shit saying that I heard the dog show where I hit the dog
They say oh look he's doing this, but when they show the video it doesn't show that
I didn't hear no fucking dog about a hitter dog. I would have went to jail. Why didn't I go to jail then?
Why didn't I go to jail? The same things they say about they keep I mean if someone has a dog those they they abuse the dog
I mean, I yeah, they did it
But what about gamble gamble did did we all not see psyche?
Did you not see the video of gamble in a song humping on a gay fat dude?
St. Oh left me so good poppy in front of a little four-year-old boy is literally like four or five feet away from him, dude
Yeah, I'm mr. Extendo. Yes, you should join if you can come up. I don't that's a joker like up. He's a good guy
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, they'll say anything brand
I mean, it's like that whatever they think will like bother you or like hurt you or like, you know, I mean
I mean to now. It's like wow and and Alex hanging out that I I'm supporting Brandon
She's she's the one that said, you know
Support him and he seemed like a nice guy because when you meet him, he's a good guy
right now she's trying to threaten me saying that i'm gonna go to jail and then
she's threatening me that she's gonna come to albuquerque and do something to me
who is nuts alex is that something yeah in seven days so that she's close to my house and in
seven days something's gonna happen that nobody is brave enough to do so what does that tell you
that's like a threat like what are you saying that you're gonna pull up on me
I but I think it's like it's like so ambiguous that it's like probably nothing you know, it's like
Yeah, I don't she's not she's trying me before according to her before I was I was gonna have to leave the country change my name
And that was like two years ago. That was two years ago
Are you there Apollo? Are you there too?
Yeah, that's that's that but she's not the type of person to go real life like that on people because she's been screwed with a lot too
because remember what happened to her two years ago when she was uh
I'll do an extruder stream. Yeah
You know, oh, and I got yeah, and I got a screenshot of gamble admitting that I've done nothing wrong because Alex last night
Gamble was in her live kissing her ass last night right after he talked to you
He was over there telling her. Oh, she was like, oh, oh, let's use these clips now. Let's get him arrested
What what if I go in person Albuquerque police department and then and then Gamble's all oh, they're horrible
He's all I've already talked to detectives and they said that they're not gonna do anything unless there's a victim
So you just admitted it right there the cops told me they're doing anything. There's no victim. What are they gonna charge me with?
There's no victim, bro
Hey, Paul, are you there?
I'm sorry, I had to fix my microphone.
I mean, Brandon and INX, yes.
Yeah, and we defend ourselves, so I have a temper too,
like Brandon, you know, that doesn't mean we're assholes,
but it's like, some of this is hurtful,
so yeah, we get pissed off and say something about it.
Well, Paul is really good about,
he understands these trolls, right, right, Apollo?
Yeah, we're learning I guess but Brandon's been doing live forever. He does his own streaming. She doesn't need to be an intern for anybody
They should intern for him. They should intern for him
Yeah, I'm the one that had a teacher how to do the live stream. She didn't even know what she was doing
Yeah, he's real good with all of that because he's also most times working at the same time
And he showed us that they're working and digging the ground he had his uniform on and he was doing will work at the same time that he was live and so he's able to multitask do all these things at once.
Yeah, yeah, I'm just sick of this, you know, and I just kind of lost it with everybody last night
It's like fuck all of you fuck you, you know, I wasn't yeah
I wasn't gonna go hard on on Alex, but threatening me to get me in jail threatening to come around me
That's that's that's on another level making weird a pictures. You know, it's just stupid
And then she reported a video of mine for privacy. I you know, I'm probably gonna report her whole channel
Later, it's just I've been dealing with this baby cat that I was worried about cuz she she was sick
Yeah, she was in hiding for a day and
Yeah, I was here yesterday. I'll day
The real pedophile is gamble gamble dated two different 16-year-old girls
Gamble's on video grooming a little 10-year-old boy bro an eight-year-old boy. He was on the news for grooming a little boy
What weirdo?
Interesting now is there any is there any normal person on this panel? It's anyone. It's a pedophile. Anyone. What's going on here?
Yeah, it's normal. There's no
She said that there's really none of us are pedophiles, but it's a cover. We say that we're actually a drug
Extortionists that's what we're doing now. Mr. Isendo is coming on the chair. There's a cold memory. Yeah
People are doing what's going on? Why aren't they all right? There's Brandon Q. We have IA next and we have Apollo
We're just we're just we're just chatting. Nobody's arguing
Yeah, I'm yeah, I'm
We're talking about a guy named Gamble in Miami who shows his butt in thongs to little boys in humson gay dudes
In front of three feet away from a little boy dude that's swimming in the water
Why are you obsessed with uh, why are you obsessed with gamble?
No, i'm not he's talking about me. He went and told alex last night. He's in the chat right now. Oh, he's bad
He's bad. That's all he does so i'm gonna expose him
Keep talking about me gambling. I'm gonna keep exposing how you how you groom those two sixteen-year-old girls
How you groom that little eight-year-old boy Daniel how you showed your asshole to that little boy in public
Well, all that shit dude all that shit bro was on like on like his show like swatting trying to swap Brandon and stuff like that
I mean, it's like doing it on the air and stuff like that. Yeah, they do swatting me like ten times, bro
Yeah, you see yeah, he swatted me like like like bro, I've been swatted probably I would say I've probably been swatted
5,000 times bro in the past two years. Oh my god
I've been swatting more than ice beside him, dude.
And he threatened to kill my cat, bro.
Yeah, I have some advice for you.
You know, I've been streaming for a while.
That guy, Gamble's been persistently in the panel verse.
Yeah.
So I don't know.
You guys maybe try not to make enemies with him.
Maybe your life will be easier.
No, he came to me
He's not he's already been on my nuts, bro. He used to go live every night to talk about me
That's the only thing he went a year straight going live every night to talk about me
He's famous for for getting his foosie tube in trouble. That's what he's famous for
Yeah, he's a coward, bro
Yeah, I thought that was funny though. I thought that was funny
You know what I got eight year old little boy named Daniel, bro
And then that little eight year old boy got arrested by the FBI for selling CP and swanning people
I mean, oh the little kid grew up to be the little boy Daniel. Uh-huh. Wow
So what does up with you guys obsession with everybody's like is it it's it's still a reoccurring thing that everyone you know
You know what cool remember? I got some good advice from a very good friend of mine
That's very careful with YouTube because she used to go on panels and stuff and she was gonna give Alex a chance
And she said well, I like what she's posting and she said give me a few days though because she always flip-flops
And so we did and so she then she said you know what I think I'll join because she did another nice video on you
And then she thought what happened yesterday, and she's happy. She never joined and she told me ignore it
That's all you got to do ignore. Don't don't react because she's been through this before a long time ago
Yeah, so now Nancy told you what are you doing talking to Crystal and Barb. I know that she told you that no
I went on to know I'm talking today today. We were she texted we you know, she's at work
Joker now
He just texted that but she's right Brandon. It's hard to do because I feel like I have to defend myself
But these are strangers so they don't matter so I had to I reread what she said a couple of times. It's like
No wonder she's she's away from this shit and they're not fucking with her at all anymore
No, I'd rebread the text it was just a text because what she said was important and it hit me it's like damn, you know, it's like she's right
Not keep reading it
To ignore ignore it
That's yeah, that's true. Sometimes you try to ignore and they still keep it up though
You know, you're right. It's like feeding the trolls and sometimes it is difficult not to because it's like, you know
We will they hit triggers. I mean they'll figure out your triggers and they'll just hit on them hit on them
Hit on them and they'll basically
But they feed on the reaction, they feed on like the, oh, I got that person on stage.
That's why, yes.
Chat always wins.
That's why Chat wins.
Look at her, she really won big because nobody ever mentions her anymore.
One person still does, but she, you know, she was about to go live about that person.
now when she saw Alex turning on all of us he said no way and she was giving me
advice and also yeah and she's out of trouble and they've forgotten about her
because I think Genville even went at her during COVID. He made a live on her
and humiliated her. Yeah, she went through hell that time because she's got a
husband and kids and
I remember it affected her and then she still did a panel one time after that and she was just so sweet and smart and
Um, yeah, and then she never went back again. She she'll watch sometimes that she stays away from it and nobody
Mentioned her anymore except for that one person
Joker you're talking to like the the the biggest crime syndicate on youtube because we're we're a mess
We're a we're a meth syndicate. We we call ourselves pedophiles just to get the attention away from our meth our meth dealings
That's the new sarcasm. Yeah. Yeah. Well, that's but it's being said seriously, but I think I mean it is
I'm saying it sarcastically, but yeah, she's saying that we're meth dealers. Yeah, we said meth was
No wonder
Yeah, thanks for saying that Brandon so it is true what my brother said she somehow reached out to him
And all of a sudden he's like, uh, yeah, he knew her. He said it was, uh, he even said her channel
I said, you know, it was like, no
And they did that side or whatever and I never told him who she was because he goes hard on people
I mean, you think somebody, you know, he gets away with a lot of shit
Can you answer me a question? Mm-hmm. What is a pocket pussy?
Pocket pussy. Does anybody know what a pocket pussy is who can the sex toy it looks like a someone writing the chat ad about
pocket pussy
Right. Okay. Well, you know, you know, J one last night he was on beat us and he said he said he wanted a pocket anus an eight inch pocket anus
Yeah, and he's and then he wanted to buy Eldo and Sam man's used pocket pussies he said
A flashlight with like a vagina on it and you fuck the flashlight kind of thing or that's the flesh I don't know
a little portable but it looks like a can it looks like a can it's a good for them right
good for you don't know we have a proper procedure those are elder elder and salmon you can get hair
attached to it congratulations uh i don't have fun with it yeah gamble's gonna be mad after today
man hey gamble suck on it dude i know you're in the chat i know you're watching
How does it make you feel that I'm still talking to Karen Gamble?
I just got a message from Alex and I should I share it?
I mean, it's like I do want to hear it like she messes up. Yeah, I said Alex
I'll leave you alone as you wish, but I didn't do anything to you. I just loved you
Wish you the best my door is always open and she goes, you know exactly what you did all you do is consume
make it about yourself and I'm just
to play victim without much regard
for others. You got that message from
me in DM that I said, you know,
keep your friendship with her.
I even said something nice about her
yesterday and then all of a sudden
I see her putting all this shit up.
And I'm not doing anything to her. What am I gonna do? I'm not gonna have I attacked her. I'm not I'm not I'm not gonna
What am I I'm not gonna attack her or do anything? So what is her problem with me?
I don't know. What is she gonna do?
Gamble have you called the police about Brandon and stuff like that?
Yeah, yeah, that's crazy dude going too far. I think with this stuff especially. I mean, how can you go from?
Just like how can the mind the human mind change so much in like a matter of ten minutes and all of a sudden
It's like completely different people completely different beliefs completely different
I mean, it's like that just seems like impossible for me to understand and I just
Yeah, I don't I don't get that either man like
And then she's saying oh something's gonna happen in six days that nobody's ever been brave enough to do like what does that mean?
I don't know. I don't think anything will happen.
They're gaslighting you, bro.
You're getting gaslighting.
Then you're going to make something happen to yourself or something.
I don't know.
Yeah, she wants me to be paranoid, but what am I paranoid?
She can't get me arrested for what?
They're manifesting gaslighting on you, dude.
They're manifesting a gamble.
Yeah, it's just a mind game. Yeah, it's a mind game.
That's all it is.
Yeah, so I can ask you this, like, Q Army, I've been streaming for a while, I used to do a lot of IRL and stuff, and uh, you know, I've talked to Gamble before, dude, why don't you just be nice to him and make friends with him?
No, I already did, I did before, I did before, and his little, and his little, one of his little members fucked it up for him.
Yeah, they've been friends they were friends like kind of for a year like for you know friends
Years and years like five years at least there's something like that Brandon
Joker or sorry mr. Extendo your IP to I believe right yeah, or yeah
I've seen Joker a lot a you're the dude people used to come in my chat with your picture. I think cuz yeah
You're the same guy. I have a few fan accounts Jim J. Hey wire. Are you Jim J? Hey wire? I don't know
Yeah, I'm gonna even Jim J. Hey wire. He's a Joker's picture. He's like Joker banned me three years ago, but um, yeah
Yeah, Jim John. Hey wire dude that guy's
That's not you
That is somebody else trolling dude. Well, yes, but um, mr. Extendo just got the ps5 pro
And so he's been on his channel playing what red dead redemption and you're playing with like a pro
of warzone today with a pro pro player and stuff and uh
Yeah, everyone check out mr. Extendo with a w mr. Extendo with a w at the end of it
That's my channel. Uh, I usually do streams now and psych every day. So I've been trying to yeah
He's been good during stream on youtube or what or on kick
Stuff is about gaming though, dude. It's all about gaming. He's on youtube. He's on youtube mr. Extendo
with a w at the end
Do you play battlefield six
Yeah, somebody in the chat said that you spread your butthole for a gamble
I spread my ass not my asshole
Yeah, but who cares what he's gonna say that's two adults I showed my ass to adults he showed his asshole to a little boy
So shut the fuck up
What's worse showing your ass to gamble or showing your asshole to a little boy in public? What's worse?
not show it at all they did come on now
they're one worse than the other obviously but it's still pretty weird
it's okay I mean they were like it was kind of like you know having
who cares he showed himself with his dick tucked in naked when he took in his
dick to look like he has a vagina
That dude ain't nobody to criticize anyone.
He ain't nobody to criticize anyone.
You show household, you show dentists, you show anything.
What's wrong?
Who cares if it's consensual and it's with adults?
Okay, do it private.
Do it private.
It is in private.
It wasn't private.
Oh.
The only people that saw it are the people that wanted to see it.
where you want this one yeah that's kinky but okay anybody's phone okay like people do that all
the time there's people that are showing their ass right now on a video call to somebody right now
yeah it was i mean it was like one of those like here's like a group chat but then they're
they're probably like saying oh do this and do this and they're probably recording and stuff
Yeah, but yeah, he was watching. Oh, he got called out bro because they're like look at the video
They're like why is he staring at it? They were like zooming in on his face gamble's eyes
They're like look he's here at it. Sorry. You see you see trolling. Is it true people show of the buttocks here?
Yeah
I hear them in discord. We show our buttholes in discord. That's what we show you. Oh my god. Oh
Hey psyche, do you remember Trump sir Bob road remember Trump sir?
Well, he was that old man that used to be in Kerman and friends bro and he used to tell people. Oh a butthole challenge
He's all he's all proved to me. Your asshole isn't blown out right now or your game you tell him
Yeah, he'd be all show your asshole and prove that it's not blown out you'd say
use that line from now on I'm gonna try to say that you don't remember that guy
the little old man and he would go live he had a kid like monkey pox at one
point he had red sores all over his face oh I started watching at least maybe a
year and a half ago so I missed that oh no yeah he was already probably around
I'm after the Jimmy the Christian and he was like a three like a three three four years ago
So Karen your INX, right?
So somebody in the chat said that you made peace with Gamble is that true? I made what?
Yeah, yeah, just so no fights or nothing cuz he actually defended me once and I forgot about that and he remembered
So like I said man, they're still going on a bush
Yeah
So you are so what's happening to you Bernie Q? What is he doing to your life to make it terrible?
He's not doing anything. He just runs his mouth online. That's it
Yeah, he just runs around
You oh, yeah, he's trying but it don't work. He's actually in hiding for me dude
He'd be locked. I have his yeah, I made him lock down his discord
He won't even turn on his camera now when he goes live. I have his whole shit locked the fuck down because of me
He can't even turn on his camera because I zoom in on his face and I say damn
Look how look how look how he's aging and he's so insecure. Then he won't get on cam after that
It's fucking hilarious, dude. He's so insecure and so easy to
To trigger man. It's so easy dude. So how did this beef start?
A long time ago well somebody was saying that I'm they're like oh your friends with gamble people the IP to people they're like
Oh, we heard you're in DX. We heard you were gamble
I said I don't even know who that is and people kept bringing it up
So I went into it. I went into his discord. I found him. I said hey, what's up motherfucker?
Who the fuck are you bro, and I just started talking shit to him, dude
But people are saying yeah, I don't give a fuck
Let him do something bro. You don't do shit. I scared of no one bro
He knows where I live where I work. He can't do anything powerless
And that's where because you have outside touching grass dude psych is touching grass
This is amazing right here.
The thing I noticed though is Brandon and Ganville love their cats because I remember
Ganville always went live with OD, his cat, a beautiful cat that I fell in love with because
that cat looked like mine and she just-
You fell in love with another person's cat?
Well, I love animals, not in love like that, but you know, love like love, I love animals.
I rescue and they mean a lot to me. So yeah, I'm an advocate here for two majors shelters here
So I'm involved with the rescue
Yes, I am an advocate. Yes, the lady that ran a big rescue
put me in as an advocate in 2012 because I was using her help to come help us and
Take the cats that we'd rescue
How the hell did you end up on psych channel if you're a
I don't know. Well, I don't know. I mean, he has good content because of
No, it was before that I've been on his panel
Oh, really? Yeah, cuz I like the AI videos that he makes and music all of that. Yeah
They're saying a bunch of terrible things about you
Losers that's gamble that's gamble and his little buddies on all it's like I said gamble we exposed you bro
Gamble I got you on video grooming a little eight-year-old boy, bro
There's nothing you can say again. Well the videos that I have want to be all sweet one of the alls because we did make peace
So it's it's a loser probably pretend. He just yeah, no. Yeah, see that's him. See he's still talking shit to you
He's not gonna be cool with you Karen. He's always gonna talk shit about you. Yeah
They only did that they saw that they saw
You know, they saw that I got mad at Alex. So they try to do the same thing to you
Yeah, guess what though? There is an app that I paid for and it'll show you who they are with the
You know with their IP the my brother knows how to do that. He taught me he used to be a dangerous
Yeah, I could do that too. I could put in the ads. Yeah, I could put in their ads and I could get the email address
They pulled up a lot of these people. That's how Rick got it because I'd give him the information and he'd start doxing them.
But yeah
Yeah, no, it's just stupid they just need to shut up get a life join panel and say it to our faces
It'll find the the account and it will go through a search or whatever it shows everything even socials
You know, it'll tell you what other websites that it'll show you other websites that that email address is registered to
Right because my brother taught me that because he used to be a hacker and he was on the news when he was nine. Yeah
And what he does is like he caught somebody and he fucked with them on the computer and he put a black screen on their computer with a message
And I have your fucking info and he showed the their home and stuff and that was another hacker that freaked out
And my brother told him oh you you got your printer running
I'm he says, um, it's you can't shut it off. But as soon as it runs, it stops running, your computer is fucked. And that's exactly what happened to them. And he never fucked with my brother. They taught him how to hack because he hacked into the NASA spaces thing. And he was too young. They were looking for him. He was nine. Yeah. And then he got these older people. Yeah, he was nine. He was in the news. They couldn't find him, though.
You know and my other brothers afraid of him show me your hacker abilities now well not right here, you know
It's easy. He's a pro at it. He'll he'll find somebody's phone number fake numbers in minutes because we there was that rescue lady that
you know that made me a
She her name well, I'm like I was there name, but I remember that
She was picking up some hats and somebody was fucking with her and they were put putting weird posts on her
Facebook saying that she kills animals and other stuff with a fake account like Demi and nobody knew who she was.
Well this person got my number and she started calling me and harassing me about that lady.
Saying y'all are gonna go to jail. She's gonna go to jail. She's a druggy and all this and I was upset and then she called my job one
time and then when I was going home my brother called me and I was pissed and he said what's wrong and I told him what happened I
Said there's this person Demi and we nobody knows who she is not even the rescue and
He said well, I'm not gonna get involved in this just ignore it
And I said she's calling again and he said what's her name and I gave him the name and the fake number
And like two minutes later, he called and he said this is all her information because I had a court case against her and she was going to be served.
So he gave me her address, her parents address and a phone number.
And then I was thinking, well, I think he said she's a receptionist at a car dealership.
He gave me the address and it was down the street from where I live.
And I said, well, that's the address I need so they can serve her there during work hours because if she's working and they go to her house, she's not going to be there.
And he did it. He did it. But guess what? After I hung up with him on the next morning, I heard that she was served. So I called her at work and sure enough, she answered.
And when she heard it was me, she freaked out and hung up.
But she's that lady that sent to you the pictures of the cat tied up under the bed
That one uh-huh and that cat because
somebody else was fostering that cat because she has fosters and
Please calm them to take the cat from that person and she had it tied it under the bed
And she wouldn't send pictures of the cat and then then I found out through another lady
That she took two dogs at the lady said hey these are rescues and
Um, you know, they need to be together though, and she said, Oh, I'll make that happen. She didn't
She she separated them
And just gave then made money off of it
Like she didn't care. She was you know, but she yes, he ended up going to jail
That's horrible, but nobody knew who she was and it's my brother. He just finds people just like that. He's just real quick
But then when he fucked with my brother
Not to interrupt you Karen, but I don't know who these people are. I just came here to join Syxtreme. Yeah
Yeah, I
Just know that I just wanted to join because I thought it was funny that Brandon was successful gamble or they're having a beat
I don't know. I think it's kind of funny. I don't really I don't know any of these
I'm not in any of these communities or anything
Here I'm just here to be here
Yeah, I know everybody tries to do that, but you get weirdo trolls that have no life and make fake accounts and
Do this 24 hours a day. I guess they're just losers
And you don't do it. Yeah, I don't mix you don't do that
No, I don't I don't do that. No
They said they said congrats on the first day of your life talking to
Just know
It's a scum. They're saying that you guys are scumbags.
They're scumbags. That's why they make fake accounts.
Yeah, that's why they can't come on their real account because we have so much dirt on them
that they need to use a fake account.
No, they're I'll ever meant a distance. They're on 24-7
They're branding you. They said you're worse than LD, dude. LD is pretty pretty pathetic
LD try to add me on IG the other day. I refuse. I blocked it
It's like how did he find my IG because I have a different name on there
Wait, what? Ask Brendan. Wait, wait, wait
Why are you hit on the first in year or five?
Oh
It's a beep beep like when you stop making like, you know, I'll stop blocking you when you're like, you know
Predator on in public and stuff like that
Okay, I don't mean people are just fucking crazy. I mean, it's like just so
It is crazy, it's crazy. It's like, you know, someone like I'm an animal lover. I have a family person
And so, you know, I don't understand what it is.
What about what Gamble said that he was going to rape a baby?
What about that?
I mean, it's just, I mean, it's like, really disgusting.
I mean, it's like, I mean, I mean, I mean, there's people that will do that.
Remember, tell the story about what Christine will say about or laugh about.
You know, I mean, it's just terrible things.
It's disgusting.
I can't, I don't want you to repeat it, but they'll say terrible things about raping,
you know,
people and stuff in people's families and then christine will laugh about it right i mean it's like
listen say if i start about christine it's gonna be a long long trust me right i know we'll meet
you okay that's why that's why i don't trust any of these panel females you don't get the
personal ionics i'm don't get involved in your personal shit okay i don't know you but all the
Crazy
Yeah, but in general on YouTube whatever this right next we're talking and I were talking today like there's just some crazy
People talk worse that they're evil. They really have no boundaries
They go way too far than the man, way too far.
Right.
Because they are anonymous in a certain way or they just think they can get away with
it because they can't prosecute it or it's difficult to prosecute like internet stuff
and stuff.
But some people do get prosecuted, you know, like the guy that was harassing me is indicted
now.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, Joker.
Good to see you.
Thanks for coming on.
I'm going to make a rumble.
Yeah, make a rumble. Yeah, rumbles. I mean, that's a good, uh, you should make a rumble. That's a I heard that's a good site
Yeah
I have one, Scythe Awakens, I think, on Rumble, and then there's, oh, there's also Panel vs.
VODs on Rumble.
That's where they play, like, betas, old shows, or, like, you know...
Oh, I heard about that.
Is that old video still there, the one about Samman, where K.K. and Barry and Tommy James
and all of them were on there?
Yeah, I'm going to make, yeah, everything, everything that she deletes is on there.
Yeah recording them while they're live see these people don't know that because you can record it from beginning to end and even you know
And then if they delete it, there's no copyright strike exactly exactly and so that's why I like to play rumble stuff sometimes or yeah
Kickin stuff like that sometimes, but yeah, I'm gonna make a rumble with all the videos at gamble
Yeah, then you can do that like they're more literally a lot more
They don't really like delete videos or like have like you know the copy of like the same like system that YouTube has for like
You know, so it's like a lot like more liberal in certain ways because it's like small your shit's like delayed so I get like lagging
I'm sorry. Hold on. Let me see
Yeah, so but how's everyone like what are you guys doing anything this weekend? What's going on like? I hope hopefully you have a
You have some
Fun stuff for the weekend. Yeah, it's summer and I've got a good tan so far
But yeah, I need to get darker. So we're gonna go there to Galveston go to the beach
Yeah, okay. What is it? I mean, it's like, I mean, I need to probably delete some uh,
some words
I put some words in the band word list in the chat. I mean, I'm not gonna say
I mean, it's just like I can't believe I don't have these words banned
You don't need to do that on rumble, huh?
No, no, you don't oh my gosh. Look at this. This is terrible. Look at this. This is terrible boo boo kitty a person like look at
Look what she does you remember them? I mean no, I mean she like though. This is her. This is her. What are they saying?
Well, this is her post about me. It's like me like homeless or something like there
I am like I'll sad and it says missing Lenore like my cat's missing and then I what does it say unemployment law office or something?
I don't know. It's like I'm always
You know what and and a streamer I don't want to say his name
He did that on Alex so he took her picture and put it up with the homeless sign above her
And she had an afro and they said it was the day after she was kicked out of the porn industry. Oh
Everybody I still have it
Yeah, I mean
Yeah, well, I think that that was about like daddy Sam
I'm a thief because okay the claim of a nine-year-old hacking NASA is a myth
But it's likely confused with the legendary true story of a 15-year-old name. Hey, man
I don't think we're talking about the NASA. I mean, that's Crystal Marie's story, right?
Crystal Maria said she mentioned the rocket like but um, which is 10 years old that she's in the Guinness Book of World Records
I don't think that that's what anybody else was talking about the the nine-year-old hacking NASA
I mean, that's not the
That was a long time ago. You know, he's grown now, but you know, oh
Next is it related to a NASA hacker? I thought they're talking about Brandon sir. I don't know
No, yes, I am he did it at nine years old. They'd never knew his name in those older
professional hackers
Um, you know they they welcomed him and they helped protect him and they never said his name and yeah he even still has that article.
Anyone who can use scripts anyone who can use some sort of scripts or some tools because he's like eleven years younger than me so he's already grown and married and he was doing this shit because he knows how to shut up your your electricity some kind of way and he did that to my brother.
And what else, he did some shit to him by hacking into his business computer and put a prostitute list on there and then called his secretary about it.
And my brother won't talk to him, to this day, he won't have shit to do with him because of that.
He won't forgive him.
He also ordered $60,000 of electronic stuff somehow by hacking.
Yeah, shade public, shade public on the screen.
That's a good idea.
Yeah, and he didn't want to do a police report because he's his brother because, you know,
so they don't talk Phil since then.
My other brother won't have shit to do with him.
He says he's dangerous.
So I better don't mess up with you, right?
No, I'm not doing anything. I'm not doing that shit. You know, it's like
I don't know. I don't know my phone acting. My phone acting. We have to
Right now. Are you doing something?
Yeah, it's like laggy. It's like laggy. It's like he's lagging.
Oh, Huckern, she's lagging.
Stop Hacking Apollo. Stop Hacking Apollo.
But it's only Psyche. It's Psyche that's delayed.
I'll be right back. I'll be right back. You guys talk.
It's only Psyche that's delayed.
It's just like delayed or something. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, Karen like I forgive you man, like yeah
I mean, I thought the dog was heard and I see you're good with your cat
You love your cat and I love it on your cat like like game
And I was only acting crazy because Gamble's friend drug me
Yeah, I was hanging out with his friend that he had break into my house when I was in the hospital
He drugged me and they took me to the hospital and pump my stomach and then when I was in the hospital
His little buddy went into my apartment and filmed all the stuff on my phone
He was showing nudes of people on my phone
Messages phone numbers docs and everybody on my whole phone while I was in the hospital
That was the purpose of doing that
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know. I mean when I talked to him yesterday
It was like he's he's made some changes like me. I have and still have other people and he seemed really cool
He wasn't that mean hateful person, you know, he's like a different person like he's grown a lot
He's still doing the same. Yeah, he's still doing the same stuff threatening older women stalking people
Even his own top mod his own top admin cats confirmed that
That he never met his fiance. It's only on discord and he's saying that he moved on but he's still stalking me
That's not moving on bro. Oh
Page is live right now, and I think I'm aroused by page
Okay, hey, let's do a rate of pages channel
So and this is a friendly rate and it's like if anyone misbehaves over there in the chat
Like I will personally like kick your ass
But I'm heard her I'll get her channel up and we can go like say hi to her and she just readings and stuff and it's gonna be fun
So you're gonna end your stream
Yeah, I'm gonna put her link up and then we can all go over there because I like to do raids of
streams and I want to help her, you know, build her channel because she has a stream for a while.
I'm going to end mine, but hold on, I'm just going to get her channel real quick and then
over there to her chat.
She just does her chat, but she does really, really good, great readings.
I really recommend if she has time and she can pull some cards for you to do that.
But she's just fun.
It's like, but bring good energy over there.
and then I'll post the channel for you guys.
And then I got it, okay?
And go over there and say hi to Paige
and I'll meet you over there.
I mean, I'll post her live actually.
And there's her live.
She looks like she's getting her cards out and stuff. So and I think you'll you'll have fun over there
I think we'll have fun. So here let's go to pages
There's really well, I'm gonna be leaving a little bit. I got a okay the rest of this
See you soon. Bye. Thanks chat. Love you